[Music]
uh
i didn't expect this place to be crowded
with so many people
and some of their dance moves my God i
can barely contain myself
i think I might rape someone before the
nights over her
what about you Sonia dunno I think I'm
just gonna go back up to the room and
read
I'm pretty tired attention
excuse me can I have your attention
everybody first off
everyone having a good time or what
all right we're gonna be starting our
karaoke challenge any minute now
so form a line if you're interested
Manic move your leg I hate to use it
like that
because I can see the silhouette of your
balls peeking out from the inside of
your shorts
hey KKnux karaoke's about to start might
want to go get in line before it gets
too big
what not in your life you go to it
singing is [ __ ] gay besides we
already know who rules the school
when it comes to music the drama club
which consists
of only two members your bro Sonic the
Hedgehog
and his most handsome man sexy lover
Bartleby
Montclair of Dresden the richest man alive
looks like karaoke's gonna be good what
do you say about going over and showing
them what the drama club is made of
don't mean am I my [ __ ] is being extra
feisty today
[ __ ] did you sneak a handful of those
free sNickerdoodles at the check-in desk
well I don't mind boys gotta read and
boys gotta read good
now let's hurry up and get in line
before somebody else is
alright are you ready spin the roulette
spit the road let's spin this set
split the road let's spin this [ __ ]
where is it gonna stop me
[Music]
where is it gonna stop [ __ ] where is
it gonna stop [ __ ]
is it your door maybe you
get the [ __ ] up here me but I don't know
how to sing
art levy I don't understand why didn't
they pick us he's a nobody
what in the world is going on that is
what I was wondering as well
wait here while daddy gets to the bottom
of the
heyo I have a bone to pick with you
can you please make it quick we have an
event going on
be quiet you know what you did you hurt
my baby boys feeling
usually it's the drama club who gets to
sing first but this time you speak to us
i want answers if you want answers i
will give them to you
it's simple it's because your boyfriend
is fat as [ __ ]
last time he got on and then stepped off
the stage the whole building started to
shake
it scared us we all thought we were in
an earthquake but it was just as huge
bouncy ass
you are no different in fact you're much
much worse
if you so much has sit down this whole
building would collapse
and kill us all except for you because
you're so [ __ ] ripped
you and your [ __ ] can't sing later
tonight after we all left
this place is planned to be bulldozed
next week anyways
so feel free to speed up the process
all right it's time to spin the roll at
one more time
who's it gonna be
wait stop no Mindy I can't not with so
many people
come on Sonia live a little it's new
year's eve
you can't sit and read a book the whole
night
come on Knux get up there
have fun you do you'll thank me later
for this or not
[Laughter]
i don't sing I can't sing I don't know
any of the lyrics
up there just follow the words up there
on the tv screen
as long as you follow along with that
you'll do just fine
living in my own world
didn't understand
that anything can happen
[Music]
stop stop singing this moment that stage
belongs to my [ __ ] bee
[Music]
so what they're not even that good man
and Bartleby can show them up in a
second
drama club all together now it's our
turn
fire tell me fire tell me where are you
bartelby wait for me where are you going
are you feeling okay my precious lover
do you need me to massage your feet
again
i'll go get the cottage cheese
no bitch it was their singing you heard
it didn't you
what did you think of it tell me spill
the beans
haha I thought it was [ __ ] [ __ ] not
like us
[ __ ] that the chin there sounds like
Zach Effron from the Disney
channel why the [ __ ] can't you sing like
that as it stands now
you run the risk of making the drama
club fail because you're not as good as
me
also every building you step into turns
into a bouncy house
because you're so fat I think so
everyone stopped coming to our shows
the least you could do is sing better
than a poopy baby
I'm I'm sorry sugar daddy I’ve been a
bad boy if that's how you feel
i'll try to go better can't you see
the time for trying is up now is the
time for results
so I have a new trading method if we
don't want those retards to steal our
glory
you're gonna have to give it everything
you got at next reside all
i mean I know I'm gonna do fine because
well
in hotel b but you [ __ ] I mean you
[ __ ] suck and I don't mean you just
suck my balls
whatever training you have in mind I'm
ready
no you're not but wigging it anyway
[Music]
something
you that was a real workout on the ass
crack good game boys
hey Johnny would you mind if I have a
drink of your h2o real quick
nah man drink up go ahead and have some
of those
electrolytes haha it's like you're
drinking my [ __ ] piss
sup guys did you have a good new year oh
hey on ox glad to see you're here so
soon for practice
i hope you're at the top of your game
why is that
you didn't forget did you the
championship is two weeks away
with you leading us to victory hey i
didn't forget
I'm just not worried at all all right
that's the spirit
[Music]
that sounded like the Bell I thought
class wasn't for another 20 minutes
just the drama club auditions apparently
the drama club's gonna have a show at
the same time has the championships
why would they do that does anybody even
care about the drama club
Knuckles you don't understand Bartleby
is there
and he made my bro his [ __ ] and slapped
his ass like six times
they practically ruled the drama club
with an iron fist now
at our last basketball game only two
people showed up because they went to
watch Bartleby the drama club instead
i see makes sense yo Manic you wanna go
check it out
we can't do that what about the game we
need to practice
Manic I didn't wanna tell you this cause
i didn't want to hurt your feelings
three black people just joined the team
aside from Johnny we're all getting
kicked out
you know black people are just better at
basketball
yeah it's like how Mexican people are
good at eating tacos and burritos and
[ __ ]
and how white people are really good at
sneaking guns into school
so they can gun [ __ ] down
hey Manic me and Johnny are going poop
in the bathroom before class
you want to come with catch you later
KKnux
I'm gonna hang out with the guys you go
ahead on to class without me we'll meet
up again at lunch
okay I heard there's gonna be pizza
let's get there quick so Bartleby
doesn't take it all to put in my bros
ass this time
Manic I don't think you should go
anywhere with them
i think they're planning something real
bad they want to separate us
get you alone why how can you say that
Knuckles
they're our friends Manic take a [ __ ]
look at him
he didn't look like that two months ago
he's been lifting weights and getting
ripped you don't get that amount of
muscles
without a purpose come on Manic hurry up
and come on I got to drop a juice
do you want me to pee and poopy myself
again
hey did you hear me I said get those
green buns over here
do you expect me to wait all day he had
a purpose in getting all Jacked up and
his purpose is
is me no your butt cheeks
your ass might as well be ground beef
because if you go with him
he's gonna pound it he's going to [ __ ]
you in your huge plump butt
Knuckles I can't believe what you're
saying you're sounding like a total
square
I'm gonna get going we'll catch up later
okay
if you find my bro tell him to stop
being a total spaz
and think about joining the b-ball team
the [ __ ] hey what the hell are you doing
over there
you're not part of the drama club
oh no no I'm not it's my brother
he's in the drama club so I was only
checking in on him
so why did you come down here to watch
the auditions
girl I just saw my best friend get
dragged off and most probably raped
by a 15 year old that's more buff than
Superman
i was going to file a police report
so you sure about this Sonia you really
want to try out for the drama club
like together yeah like what's the worst
thing that could happen
that we don't make the callbacks I don't
know it's just
well you know the drama club is kinda
gay isn't it
the rest of the basketball team are
already questioning my sexuality
because I stare at Manic's butt hey ha
of course the drama club is gay
the only members are my bro Sonic and
his boyfriend
Bartleby Montclair of Dresden the
richest man in the entire school
now let's hurry and find the seat i
think Bartleby and Sonic are going to
be rehearsing any minute
hey piano boy I told you reversals are
going to be starting any minute
you know which [ __ ] song I want you
to play right the one that makes me
sound my best
now that's what I'm talking about start
playing that [ __ ]
alright bitch you know the rules drop
the [ __ ] pants it's hard to believe
that I couldn't see you were always
right beside me these
[Music]
never feelings someone as good for me as
you
no one like you stole me before
i finally found what I’ve been looking
for
you hearing that shits on you listen to
that and tell me again we should try out
for the drama club
we are just not at the same level
Bartleby is not even close
maybe with practice we could get better
than your bro Sonic but we'll never
surpass Bartleby
[Music]
okay Manic you ready to take a [ __ ]
dump in here
where nobody can hear us actually
now that I think about it I don't really
have to go anymore
so if you guys would move out of the way
i need to get going to have lunch
well nobody's stopping you friend go
ahead try opening the door
okay wait
something's wrong I i can't get it open
it's locked
help me open the door
no one's coming to save you Manic we've
been planning this moment all year long
but why what are you planning to do with
me
is it not obvious it's because I have a
crush on you Manic
and I hid these feelings from you ever
since you joined the b-ball team ever
since I first laid eyes on you
i love you but you never noticed me i
even styled my hair
to look like your bro Sonic and you
still never acknowledged my affection
for your
green plump cheeks and then I realized
you don't need someone's approval to
rape them
[Music]
what are you doing standing around
Richard help me get those pants off
before a teacher comes by
are you sure we should be doing this bro
i mean what if a teacher comes by and
sees us
what will we do then
I'm so bored I guess I will search the
interwebs and see what's happening while
i poop
yeehaw it looks like Tamers12345
uploaded a new video
i haven't been this excited since last
week's slowdown
what in tarnation that's me on the can
what on God's flat green earth is going
on here
i need to scroll back and get myself
caught on what's happening in this video
oh no they're going to rape that boy
Manic
magic you have to run away oh no I don't
think he can hear me over the sounds of
my running [ __ ]
i have to go out there myself it's too
bad I don't have time to wipe my butt
the desperate times call for guest
protections
Richard come on grab his other pants leg
i ain't leaving without cramming this
ass
how about you grab mine instead
step away from that kid I may be on the
same basketball team as you
but that doesn't mean i'll tolerate what
you do with that boy's butthole
damn it Richard go stop him don't let
him tell on
us
hurry up and go hurry to the cafeteria
and get your pizza
i will be okay just hurry and run
my own secret obsession and it's making
me lose control
oh someday I hope to make the perfect
creme brulee
listen well I'm ready to tell about a
need that I cannot deny
dude there's no explanation for this
awesome
[Music]
[Applause]
no dude it's like a giant violin
do you have to wear a costume cutting
[Music]
tie
this is not what I planned
[Music]
is
[Applause]
[Music]
keep your voice down
why is everybody staring at you not me
you because of the callbacks
i can't have people staring at me i
really can't
[Music]
[Applause]
testing testing this is the school
intercom we have an
important announcement regarding the
drama club if you participated in the
music tryout
please head over to your nearest
classroom and check the bulletin board
to see if you receive a call back
pull up your pants bitch we got places
to be and things to see
now let's see what we have [ __ ] read it
to me
what no I don't understand why does it
say I don't believe it
we're the only two club members how can
they turn us down
should we go ask the teacher there has
to be some kind of mishap
Bartleby I'm scared singing and being
your sugar baby is all I'm good at doing
kKnux look we did it
we're the best
hey teacher teacher I need to have a
word with your ass
come on in Bartleby the doors open
all right teach I want answers and i
want them now
why'd you do it do you have reason to
spike me
to anger me how could you let those two
get a call back and notice
you stupid [ __ ] me and my [ __ ] are
the only openly gay people in this
school
the drama club is only for gay people
not outsiders
first off how dare you assume I'm gay
what would even make you come to that
conclusion
it better not be because you caught me
sucking the principal's balls
because that was only nine times
and one was an accident
hey that looks like Bartleby that looks
like the picture of my bro that I lost
last week
not now [ __ ] I'm in the middle of
something
i see I know what this is about
Bartleby you want to know why the two
show you didn't get a call back
listen I'm not supposed to tell you why
but that'll be because you are like a
son to me
i will fill you in on this [ __ ] the
truth is
you two as a duo you always just
barely passed each time and since
nobody ever tried out you were the only
two
i could pick Bartleby you're absolutely
amazing
but your [ __ ] well to put it kindly
he [ __ ] sucks and he is holding you
back
[ __ ] now that I think about it since
new year's your dancing wasn't as good
as before
why do you think that is have you not
done your daily stretches like I told
you to
I'm sorry I'm not up to par Bartleby
it's just that when you whipped my butt
it hurts to run dance or even sit i
guess you could say
that is but it's all your fault yes
i agree and I am really mad at you
thanks for your input teach looks like
my [ __ ] has a lot of training to do
before I even think about letting him
try out at the next audition
all right places places people move that
box over there
remember we only have one shot at this
let's try not to [ __ ] this one up
wow that's so certainly a lot of people
i didn't think so many would come
hey Sonia the batteries in my mic are
dead
let me borrow one of yours hey I'm
talking to you [ __ ]
sorry I'm just a big crowd shy I never
performed in front of a crowd this big
before
that's it it's easy just follow what i
do
and you should be fine after all with
your bro in the drama club you should
have learned a thing
or two by watching him
Knuckles Sonia we're getting ready to
draw the curtains
get in your spots
[Music]
flying there's not a star in
Heaven that we can't reach
if we're trying someone breaking free
you know the world can see us
in a way that's different than who we
[Music]
are
gives me strength
[Music]
where are you going and what are you
doing with that cardboard box
what do you think I'm doing bleach
because you got us kicked out of the
drama club
we can't practice my singing in the
auditorium anymore
so I'm going to sing out here in the
hallway instead so
everyone can hear my beautiful voice now
put your plump blueberry as cheeks to
work
and run around the school see if you can
find anyone who wants to listen to me
i want a full crowd in two minutes flat
but Bartleby it's one o'clock in the
afternoon
everybody else is in class did I [ __ ]
stood the bitch
[Music]
it starts with one thing I don't know
why it doesn't even matter how hard you
try keep that in mind I designed this
rhyme to explain in due
time all I know time is a valuable thing
watch it fly by as the pendulum swings
watch it count down to the end of the
day the clock takes life away it's so
unreal it didn't look out below watch
the time go right out the window trying
to hold on
but didn't even know it wasted at all
just to watch everything inside and even
though I tried
it all fell apart what invented me will
eventually be a memory of the time when
i tried
[Music]
and got so far but in the end
it doesn't even matter I had to
fight to lose it all
[Music]
one thing I don't know why it doesn't
even matter how hard to try
keep that in mind holy [ __ ] everybody my
friend
Charles just texted me and said the most
popular kid in school
Bartleby is singing right now out in
the hallway
[Music]
[Applause]
why are you all cheering for me my [ __ ]
was the one who went to get all of you
you should be cheering for him instead
[Applause]
Bartleby I now realize I made a terrible
mistake
kicking you and Sonic out of the drama
club
please please come back nobody in this
school has a voice as beautiful and sexy
as you
well what are you waiting for everybody
let's go into the gymnasium and
celebrate bottle biz return to the drama
club
the other teachers are already setting
up the party
there's enough audios and bushes baked
beans for everyone
together
[Music]
is
together
[Music]
is
that's the way it
[Applause]
[Music]